

CHRISTINE PABLO

VISUAL DESIGNER
FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO

www.seepablo.com

EMAIL

christine.pablo@gmail.com

PHONE

312.479.3154

SKILLS

/ PROFICIENT

Photoshop Illustrator UX/UI HTML CSS/SASS Powerpoint

/ WORKING

InDesign JavaScript Node Git

/ LEARNING

ReactJS

/ SOFT

Creativity
Problem Solving
Collaborative
Communication
Adapability

I'm a user-focused visual designer and front-end developer with a Flash motion background. With 10+ years working in small and large agency environments, I enjoy collaborating with others as well as working independently. My goal is to integrate technology with design to solve problems and provide a delightful user experience.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE FRONT END DEVELOPER / 2018 - present

Designed and built a mobile-first self-care website. Front-end design lead on a dog-sharing service website. Managed cryptocurrency web project.

FREELANCE VISUAL DESIGNER / 2013 - present

Redesigned and built, via CMS, websites for small businesses. One site saw increased membership by 80%. Batch designed and packaged online display ads. Designed and built email blasts using Constant Contact EMS. Created Powerpoint presentations for top PR agency and pharma clients.

FLASH MOTION DESIGNER

Razorfish, Chicago IL / 2008 - 2013

Animated and optimized online display ads according to media buy specs. Prepared and packaged ads for deployment. Collaborated with social media team in creating editorial content.

DESIGNER

Wire Stone LLC, Chicago IL / 2006 - 2008

Collaborated with client and their vendors in creation of assets for use in product video launches, large format displays, and other various marketing materials. Responsible for management and handling of unreleased client product.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Certification / 2018 UCF Continuing Education, Orlando FL

Associate of Science, Digital Arts and Design / 2006
Full Sail University, Winter Park FL

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Fashion Design / 2000 Savannah College of Art and Design, Savannah GA